POKEN RECORDS SPINNING FAST HEADLINES NEVER FADE
DEPORT A DREAM IN SILENCE TRAIN HOPE FOR BARICADE
CORTS ARE CLOTHED FOR BISNETTAS JUST THIS OUT OF STOCK
TARE THE WELL-KILLED BANNER GOWN KEEP THE FUTURE LOCKED
LOOK AT WHAT WE'VE COME TO NOW PROMISES ARE HALLOWED OUT
BUILDING WALLS AROUND OUR PIDE TRADING TRUTH FOR DOLLAR SIGHTS
JUST US FOR ALL OR NOT AT ALL WATCH THE PORTERS RISE
SEE THE CONSCIONS FALL BRAKERS TORN BRIGHT TONIGHT
SPREAD THE WHEEL TIL THE TRUTH IS DIED OHS AND WALLS RINGING OUT
ASSIGN AWAY THE FUTURE TIGENTS ON A LIST DEPORT A HUNDRED THOUSAND
JUSTICE DON'T EXIST STUDE IT SPEAK AND LOSE IT ALL
VOICES ARE NUDE FREEDOM'S JUST A SLUGGED
IF YOU'RE NOT IN THE SUIT RUBBER STAMPS FOR THE CHOSEN FEW
BLIND EYES AT 'EM LET IT THROUGH FROM WORLDS WATCHING WHILE WE STALL
BUT WHO'S LEFT TO MAKE THE CALL JUST US FOR ALL OR NOT AT ALL
WATCH THE PORTERS RISE SEE THE CONSCION FALL
BRAKERS TORN BRIGHT TONIGHT SPREAD THE WHEEL TIL THE TRUTH IS DIED
OHS AND WALLS RINGING OUT